[Applause]
[Music]
part two now let us begin with question
number
seven number seven when are you leaving
for the
airport a there's no
fee B around
11:00 C does this bus go to the airport
number eight could I get your opinion on
something a the cover
layout B
certainly C no I don't have
any number nine what's the cost of a car
wash here a yes we do b six
C buy a
machine number 10 how did you find out
about my aerobics
Class A I saw your newspaper
ad B my friend is in good
shape c that sounds
interesting number 11 your Symphony
tickets are for the main floor right a
the violin is still for
sale B I'll clean it up right
away C actually there for the
balcony number 12 why didn't we receive
more sweaters from the
supplier a because of a distribution
issue B yes yes it looks great on
you see no I don't see any
here number 13 how do I report a lost
piece of
luggage a yes this is the last one B
there's a form to fill out C that's what
the reporter told me
number 14 what are the qualifications of
the
position a a finance degree and two
years
experience B yes let's offer him the
job C I work as a human resources
manager number 15 you know how to adjust
the copier settings don't you a it's in
the main conference room B I have my own
copy C Tammy can assist you with
that number 16 could you review the
latest manuscript sent in by the
author a a number of
Errors B I'm working on that
now see it's a classic mystery story
number 17 how many microphones can we
get for the
debate a some local
politicians B I'll ask the sound
engineer C yes since the auditorium is
large number 18 where should consumers
send the recalled items
a check the manufacturer's
website b a problem with the heating
device C by the end of the
year number 19 who called you in the
middle of the advisory
meeting a my auto
mechanic B it's a promising
proposal C I would advise against
that number 20 it seems that we weren't
given enough towels in our hotel
room a there is a free shuttle there b
I'll call the front
desk see there are a few rooms
available number 21 would you like a
subscription for 6 months saw one
year a I couldn't agree
more B A Woodworking
magazine C what's the difference in
price number 22 when will the new
business cards be
delivered a not until
Friday B no my name was spelled wrong C
for the sales team
members number 23 do you think forming a
partnership is a good
idea a thanks I worked hard on it B we'd
better ask the rest of the
team C at yesterday's board
meeting number 24 why don't we designate
parking spots for the management
team a to show our
appreciation B I usually park on the
street C there's hardly room for the
customers number 25 I'm disappointed
with how the negotiations
went a representatives from both
sides B in the annual licensing
contract see oh really what
happened number 26 isn't this parking
pass valid for all areas of the sports
complex a we accept credit
cards b a large moving
truck C no just for the East lot
number 27 can I download the application
form from your
website a a paper copy can be sent to
you B Jason is still loading some boxes
on a
cart C you were selected for an
interview number 28 who would like to
lead the training session for the
interns next
week a the train departs
shortly B 3 months in
total C I'm going to a
conference number 29 why haven't the gas
bills for March been sent out yet a gas
appliances can be more
efficient B to every customer in the
area
see we're investigating the problem
now number 30 where can I get
information about moving out
early a I usually wake up before 6 in
the
morning B it should be explained in your
lease
agreement C they moved the furniture to
the fourth floor
number 31 shouldn't the new sofas for
the waiting room be here by
now a she doesn't have time to wait B
they are out of
stock C no I don't need to sit down
[Music]
number seven when are you leaving for
the
airport a there's no
fee B around
11:00 C does this bus go to the
airport number eight could I get your
opinion on
something a the cover
layout B
certainly C no I don't have
any number nine what's the cost of a car
wash here a yes we
do B
$6 C buy a machine
number 10 how did you find out about my
aerobics
Class A I saw your newspaper
ad B my friend is in good
shape c that sounds
interesting number 11 your Symphony
tickets are for the main floor right a
the violin is still for
sale B I'll clean it up right
away see actually there for the
balcony number 12 why didn't we receive
more sweaters from the
supplier a because of a distribution
issue B yes it looks great on
you see no I don't see any here
number 13 how do I report a lost piece
of
luggage a yes this is the last one B
there's a form to fill out C that's what
the reporter told
me number 14 what are the qualifications
of the
position a a finance degree and 2 years
EXP
experience B yes let's offer him the
job C I work as a human resources
manager number 15 you know how to adjust
the copier settings don't you a it's in
the main conference room B I have my own
copy see Tammy can assist you with that
number 16 could you review the latest
manuscript sent in by the
author a a number of
Errors B I'm working on that
now see it's a classic mystery
Story number 17 how many microphones can
we get for the debate
a some local
politicians B I'll ask the sound
engineer C yes since the auditorium is
large number 18 where should consumers
send the recalled
items a check the manufacturer's
website b a problem with the heating
device C
by the end of the
year number 19 who called you in the
middle of the advisory
meeting a my auto
mechanic B it's a promising
proposal C I would advise against
that number 20 it seems that we weren't
given enough towels in our hotel
room a there is a free shuttle there b
I'll call the front
desk see there are a few rooms
available number 21 would you like a
subscription for 6 months or one
year a I couldn't agree
more B A Woodworking magazine
C what's the difference in
price number 22 when will the new
business cards be
delivered a not until
Friday B no my name was spelled wrong C
for the sales team
members number 23 do you think forming a
partnership is a good
idea a thanks I worked hard on it B we'd
better ask the rest of the
team C at yesterday's board
meeting number 24 why don't we designate
parking spots for the management
team a to show our
appreciation B I usually park on the
street see there's hardly room for the
customers number 25 I'm disappointed
with how the negotiations
went a representatives from both
sides B in the annual licensing
contract C oh really what happened
number 26 isn't this parking pass valid
for all areas of the sports
complex a we accept credit
cards b a large moving truck C no just
for the East
Lot Number 27 can I download the
application form from your website
a a paper copy can be sent to you B
Jason is still loading some boxes on a
cart C you were selected for an
interview number 28 who would like to
lead the training session for the
interns next week a the train departs
shortly B 3 months in
total C I'm going to a
conference number 29 why haven't the gas
bills for March been sent out yet a gas
appliances can be more
efficient B to every customer in the
area C we're investigating the problem
now
number 30 where can I get information
about moving out
early a I usually wake up before 6:00 in
the
morning B it should be explained in your
lease
agreement C they moved the furniture to
the fourth
floor number 31 shouldn't the new sofas
for the waiting room be here by
now a he doesn't have time to wait B
they are out of
stock C no I don't need to sit
down for